Guide to the Washington Office on Africa Records - Addendum B
Yale University Divinity School Library
Washington Office on Africa Records - Addendum B
1970-1999
RG 105B
Yale University Divinity School Library
35
(74 boxes)
This collection is an addendum to the publications, correspondence, reports, statements, and collected material documenting the work of the Washington Office on Africa found in Record Groups 105 and 105A. The Washington Office on Africa was founded in 1972 to support the movement for freedom from white-minority rule in southern Africa. Its activities have included the monitoring of Congressional legislation and executive policies and actions, as well as the publication of action alerts and other documentation designed to advance progressive legislation and policy on southern Africa. Supported by church bodies and unions, the WOA has worked in partnership with colleagues in Africa, the Africa advocacy community in the United States, and grassroots organizations concerned with various aspects of African affairs.
Washington Office on Africa
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of the Washington Office on Africa, 2002.
Conditions Governing Access
Open to qualified researchers.
Biographical / Historical
See the finding aid for Record Group 105.
Scope and Contents
Series I, Regional and Country Files, is divided subseries that reflect various geographical subdivisions. These files contain materials documenting political, social, and economic affairs in the regions and countries specified.
Series II, Issues, which contains material arranged alphabetically by issue, complements the geographically arranged files of Series I.
Series III, Advocacy, contains Washington Office on Africa publications, correspondence, and documentation of participation in groups and events related to the issues of concern to WOA.
Series IV, United States Policy, contains documentation related to U.S. politics and Congressional hearings, laws, and correspondence related to Africa issues.
Arrangement
I. Regional and Country Files, 1970-1995
II. Issues, 1972-1995
III. Advocacy, 1972-1996
IV. United States Policy, 1989-1995
Church and state -- United States; Lobbying -- Law and legislation -- United States; Angola -- Politics and government; Mozambique -- Politics and government; Namibia -- Politics and government; South Africa -- Politics and government; Washington Office on Africa
- Regional and Country Files, 1970-1995; Series I
  - Africa in general
    - Articles on Democracy, 1990-1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Articles on Debt and Crime, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Articles, 1992-1995 (Box 1, Folder 3-8)
    - Analyses and Editorials, AA01, 03, 05, 1989-1994 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Development, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Drought AA02, 1983-1987, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 11-13)
    - Economics AA Africa. Dev. Bank, 1989-1994 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Economics, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Environment, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Famine AA05, 1985-1989 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Famine, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Health AA17, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Human Rights AA18, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Human Rights, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Military AA19, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Politics general AA20, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Politics, Japan, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Politics OAU AA21, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Refugees AA22, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Refugees, 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Relations: Arab Countries AA06, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Relations: Cuba AA08, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Relations: France AA09, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Relations: Hong Kong, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Relations: Intra-Africa, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Relations: Portugal AA13, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Relations: United Nations and World, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Relations: United Nations and World, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Relations: US, USSR, W. Germany(1978), 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Foreign Relations, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Social Culture AA23, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - U.S. CIA AA24, 1975-1981 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Regions of Africa
    - Central Africa General, 1992-1995 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - East Africa General, 1992-1995 (Box 5, Folder 41-44)
    - Horn of Africa, 1992-1995 (Box 5, Folder 45-47)
    - North Africa General, 1990-1995 (Box 6, Folder 48-51)
    - Southern Africa, 1986-1995 (Box 6, Folder 52-56)
    - Southern Africa Documents/ Publications, 1986-1988 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Southern Africa General - Politics, 1970-1980 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Southern Africa General-Media Center (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Southern Africa General, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - West Africa General, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 61-65)
    - West Africa, documents, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - West Africa General, 1992-1994 (Box 8, Folder 67-68)
    - West Africa General, 1995 (Box 75, Folder 787)
  - Countries
    - Algeria
      - General, 1992-1995 (Box 8, Folder 69-72)
    - Angola
      - Angola, Namibia, South Africa, 1981-1984 (Box 9, Folder 73)
      - Angola: Questions and Notes, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 74)
      - Angola Chronologies AA45, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 75)
      - General, 1987-1992 (Box 9, Folder 76-81)
      - General, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 82-87)
      - General, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 88-93)
      - General, 1992-1995 (Box 12, Folder 94-97)
      - Angola, 1995 (Box 75, Folder 792)
      - Angola, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 98)
      - Angolan War Chronology, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 99)
      - Angola: Economy (US Corporation: Gulf Oil), 1971-76 (Box 12, Folder 100)
      - Angola Economics: Oil: Gulf Oil, 1970-74 (Box 12, Folder 101)
      - Angola: Economy, Gulf Oil, 1974-1978 (Box 12, Folder 102)
      - Angola: Economics: Rail Corridor AA30, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 103)
      - Angola: Economy-oil, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 104)
      - Angola Foreign Relations: Western Europe: Portugal, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 105)
      - Angola Foreign Relations: Africa: Africa, 1975-76 (Box 13, Folder 106)
      - Angola Foreign Relations: United Nations, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 107)
      - Angola: Foreign Relations: China, USSR, Cuba, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 108)
      - Angola For. Rel. USSR and E. Bloc, 1981-1983 (Box 13, Folder 109)
      - Angola Foreign Relations: S. Africa Attacks (Box 13, Folder 110)
      - Angola Foreign Relations Negotiations AA345, 1988/89 (Box 13, Folder 111)
      - Angola Foreign Relations Negotiations (Box 13, Folder 112)
      - Angola Foreign Relations Negotiations (Box 13, Folder 113)
      - Angola Foreign Relations: US AA40, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 114)
      - Angola Foreign Relations: (Box 14, Folder 115)
      - Angola Foreign Relations: Cuba AA33, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 116)
      - Angola Foreign Relations: Socialist Camp. AA35, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 117)
      - Angola Foreign Relations: Intra Africa (Box 14, Folder 118)
      - Angola Foreign Relations: the West (Box 14, Folder 119)
      - Angola: Media, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 120)
      - Angola: Military: UNITA, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 121)
      - Angola: Military, 1975-76 (Box 14, Folder 122)
      - Angola: Military, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 123)
      - Angola: Military, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 124)
      - Angola: Military Mercenaries, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 125)
      - Angola: Military South African Invasion, 1975-1983 (Box 15, Folder 126-131)
      - Angola: Military: UNITA, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 132)
      - Angola Military South African attacks AA46, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 133)
      - Angola Military UNITA Attacks AA47, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 134)
      - Angola: MPLA, 1974-1977 (Box 15, Folder 135)
      - Angola Policy Framework, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 136)
      - Angola: Politics Unita, 1984-1989 (Box 16, Folder 137-138)
      - Angola Political Portuguese Colonial Rule, no date (Box 16, Folder 139)
      - Angola Politics MPLA:: Statement by President Neto, 1976-1977 (Box 16, Folder 140)
      - Angola Politics: education and health care, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 141)
      - Angola: Portuguese coup, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 142)
      - Angola Politics MPLA: Chipenda Factions, 1974-1979 (Box 16, Folder 143)
      - Angola Politics FPLA `, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 144)
      - Angola Politics FLEC, 1976-1978 (Box 16, Folder 145-146)
      - Angola Politics, 1974-1980 (Box 16, Folder 147-148)
      - Angola Politics: general (Box 16, Folder 149)
      - Angola Politics: program, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 150)
      - Angola Politics UNITA AA49, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 151)
      - Angola: Red Cross, refugees, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 152)
      - Angola Religion AA50, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 153)
      - Angola Social Relations AA52, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 154)
      - Angola: Target Angola, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 155)
      - Angola UNITA (Morocco) AA55, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 156)
      - Angola UNITA Savimbi 86-US6 AA57, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 157)
      - Angola UNITA Savimbi's June, 1988 US visit AA57.5 (Box 17, Folder 158)
      - Angola UNITA General AA54, 1986-1989 (Box 17, Folder 159)
    - Benin - Morocco
      - Benin, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 160)
      - Botswana General ABO3, 1987-1994 (Box 17, Folder 161-162)
      - Botswana, 1992 (Box 75, Folder 793)
      - Botswana Economics AB02, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 163)
      - EIU: Botswana, Lesotho, Swaziland-profile, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 164)
      - Burkina Faso, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 165)
      - Burundi, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 166-167)
      - Cameroon, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 168)
      - Cameroon: Anglophone Movement, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 169)
      - Central Republic of Africa, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 170)
      - Chad, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 171)
      - Congo, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 171a)
      - Djibouti, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 172)
      - Egypt, 1993-1997 (Box 18, Folder 173-174)
      - Equatorial Guinea, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 175)
      - Eritrea, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 176)
      - Eritrea, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 177)
      - Ethiopia, 1993-1995 (Box 19, Folder 178-179)
      - Gabon, 1992-9 (Box 19, Folder 180)
      - Gambia:, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 181)
      - Ghana, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 182)
      - Guinea, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 183)
      - Indian Ocean, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 184)
      - Ivory Coast, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 185)
      - Kenya: Documents and publications on, 1991-1993 (Box 19, Folder 186-187)
      - Kenya, 1994-1993 (Box 19, Folder 188-188a)
      - Kenya: publications, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 189)
      - Kenya: Denis Afande statement on Kizito Massacre, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 190)
      - Lesotho Economics AL02, 1987-1988 (Box 20, Folder 191)
      - Lesotho for. Relations AL03, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 192)
      - Lesotho General AL04, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 193)
      - Lesotho for. Relations South Africa, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 194)
      - Lesotho Military South Africa attacks, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 195)
      - Lesotho Politics ALO6, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 196)
      - Lesotho, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 197)
      - Liberia, 1992-1995 (Box 20, Folder 198-201)
      - Libya, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 279)
      - Malawi AM01, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 202)
      - Malawi, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 203)
      - Malawi, documents on, 1992-1994 (Box 20, Folder 204)
      - Malawi, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 205)
      - Malawi, 1993-1995 (Box 21, Folder 206-210)
      - Mali, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 211)
      - Mauritania, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 212)
      - Morocco, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 213)
    - Mozambique
      - General, 1974-1988 (Box 21, Folder 214-218)
      - General, 1989-1992 (Box 22, Folder 219-222)
      - Mozambique Testimony, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 223)
      - General, 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 224-226)
      - General, 1987-1996 (Box 23, Folder 227-228)
      - Mozambique Analyses, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 229)
      - Mozambique Economics: General, 1984-1988 (Box 23, Folder 230)
      - Mozambique Economics: Foreign, 1986-1989 (Box 23, Folder 231)
      - Mozambique Economics: Infrastructure, 1986-1988 (Box 23, Folder 232)
      - Mozambique Economics: Natural Disaster, 1983-1987 (Box 23, Folder 233)
      - Mozambique Economics: Refugees, 1986-1988 (Box 23, Folder 234)
      - Mozambique Editorial, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 235)
      - Mozambique and South African Economics, 1976-1977 (Box 23, Folder 236)
      - Mozambique Foreign Relations: Soviet Union, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 237)
      - Mozambique Foreign Relations: U.K./Europe, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 238)
      - Mozambique Foreign Relations US, 1985-1989 (Box 23, Folder 239)
      - Mozambique Foreign Relations South Africa Politics, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 240)
      - Mozambique Foreign Relations South Africa, 1984-1989 (Box 23, Folder 241)
      - Mozambique Foreign Relations General and USSR, 1987-1989 (Box 23, Folder 242)
      - Mozambique Foreign Relations General (Box 24, Folder 243)
      - Mozambique Foreign Relations Africa, 1986-1989 (Box 24, Folder 244)
      - Mozambique Foreign Relations EEC, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 245)
      - Mozambique Foreign Relations ANC, 1983-1987 (Box 24, Folder 246)
      - Mozambique Human Conditions EDICESA Report, 1987-1988 (Box 24, Folder 247)
      - Mozambique Independence, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 248)
      - Mozambique Revolution (Box 24, Folder 249)
      - Mozambique Transitional Government, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 250)
      - Mozambique Military Ceasefire, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 251)
      - Mozambique Military, 1983-1988 (Box 24, Folder 252)
      - Mozambique Military- MNR Raids, 1981-1989 (Box 24, Folder 253)
      - Mozambique Military- South Africa Attacks, 1983-1985 (Box 24, Folder 254)
      - Mozambique MNR, 1985-1988 (Box 24, Folder 255-257)
      - Mozambique Politics- General, 1983-1988 (Box 25, Folder 258)
      - Mozambique-Aid, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 259)
      - Mozambique Politics-Anti-Government, non-MNR, 1983-1987 (Box 25, Folder 260)
      - Mozambique Politics- Analyses, 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 261)
      - Mozambique: Portuguese in, general, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 262)
      - Mozambique Religion- General, 1973-1988 (Box 25, Folder 263)
      - Mozambique: RENAMO, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 264)
      - Mozambique Revolution, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 265)
      - Mozambique- Social, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 266)
      - Mozambique: U.N. Commission on Aid to Mozambique, 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 267-268)
      - Mozambique, women in, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 269)
      - Mozambique-drought, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 270)
      - Mozambique-lobbyists (Box 25, Folder 271)
      - Mozambique-trade unions (Box 25, Folder 272)
      - Mozambique-invisible crimes (Box 26, Folder 273)
      - Mozambique-press clips, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 274)
      - Mozambique-lobyists visits, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 275)
      - Mozambique-defense and aid fund (Box 26, Folder 276)
      - Mozambique-foreign and US investment (Box 26, Folder 277)
      - Mozambique-contacts (Box 26, Folder 278)
    - Namibia
      - General, 1981-1989 (Box 26, Folder 280-285)
      - General, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 285)
      - Namibia-ELCA, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 286)
      - General, 1991-1993 (Box 26, Folder 287-289)
      - Namibia, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 290)
      - Namibia Communications Center, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 291-292)
      - Namibia Conflict, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 293)
      - Namibia DTA General, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 294)
      - Namibia Economy, 1972-1987 (Box 27, Folder 295)
      - Namibia Economy General, 1975-1988 (Box 27, Folder 296)
      - Namibia Economy US General / Oil, 1975-1983 (Box 27, Folder 297)
      - Namibia Economy US Diggs vs Dent, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 298)
      - Namibia Economy US Del Monte, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 299)
      - Namibia Economy US AMAX, 1974-1982 (Box 27, Folder 300)
      - Namibia Economy Strikes, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 301)
      - Namibia Economy Sealskins, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 302)
      - Namibia Economy Oil Industry, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 303)
      - Namibia Economy Mining Tsumeb, 1971-1980 (Box 27, Folder 304)
      - Namibia Economy Mining General, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 305)
      - Namibia Economy Foreign Investment, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 306)
      - Namibia Economy Fishing, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 307)
      - Namibia Economy Analyses, 1980-1982 (Box 28, Folder 308)
      - Namibia Election, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 309)
      - Namibia Foreign Relations, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 310)
      - Namibia Foreign Relations UN, 1981-1988 (Box 28, Folder 311)
      - Namibia Foreign Relations South Africa, 1981-1987 (Box 28, Folder 312)
      - Namibia Independence Link / Settlement, 1981-1988 (Box 28, Folder 313)
      - Namibia Independence General, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 314)
      - Namibia Independence Analyses, 1980-1988 (Box 28, Folder 315)
      - Namibia Independence Analysis, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 316)
      - Namibia Independence US Relations, 1985-1987 (Box 28, Folder 317)
      - Namibia Independence London Oxfam, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 318)
      - Namibia Independence UN Security Council on UNTAG, 1988-1989 (Box 28, Folder 319)
      - Namibia seminar on transnatgional corperations, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 320)
      - Namibia seminar on transnatgional corperations, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 321)
      - Namibia Information Service, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 322)
      - Namibia Internal Affairs, 1984-1986 (Box 29, Folder 323)
      - Namibia Military Deserters, 1970-1977 (Box 29, Folder 324)
      - Namibia Military Mercenaries, 1980-1981 (Box 29, Folder 325)
      - Namibia Military General, 1980-1988 (Box 29, Folder 326-327)
      - Namibia Military General, 1980-1982 (Box 29, Folder 327)
      - Namibia Military Raid SA Angola / Nam, 1981-1988 (Box 29, Folder 328)
      - Namibia Newsletters, 1983-1990 (Box 29, Folder 329)
      - Namibia Politics General, 1981-1989 (Box 29, Folder 330)
      - Namibia Politics General, 1983-1984 (Box 29, Folder 331)
      - Namibia Politics General, 1982-1988 (Box 29, Folder 332)
      - Namibia Politics Foreign Relations Canada, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 333)
      - Namibia Politics SWA Propaganda, 1983-1985 (Box 29, Folder 334)
      - Namibia Politics UN, 1983-1987 (Box 29, Folder 335)
      - Namibia White Politics, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 336)
      - Namibia - General-white politics, 1981-1988 (Box 29, Folder 337)
      - Namibia-attacks on church (Box 30, Folder 338)
      - Namibia Repression- Detention, 1981-1988 (Box 30, Folder 339)
      - Namibia Repression- Flogging Cases, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 340)
      - Namibia Repression- General, 1978-1988 (Box 30, Folder 341)
      - Namibia Repression- Torture, 1977-1985 (Box 30, Folder 342)
      - Namibia Repression- Torture, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 343)
      - Namibia Resistance General, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 344)
      - Namibia Social Analyses, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 345)
      - Namibia Social General, 1986-1988 (Box 30, Folder 346)
      - Namibia Social Health, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 347)
      - Namibia SWAPO GEN, 1980-1988 (Box 30, Folder 348)
      - Namibia SWAPO GEN, 1980-1988 (Box 30, Folder 349)
      - Namibia SWAPO General, 1980-1988 (Box 30, Folder 350)
      - Namibia SWAPO General, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 351)
      - Namibia SWAPO General (Box 30, Folder 352)
      - Namibia SWAPO Analyses (Box 30, Folder 353)
      - Namibia SWAPO Detainees, 1984-1988 (Box 30, Folder 354)
      - Namibia SWAPO East Block, 1975-1984 (Box 30, Folder 355)
      - Namibia SWAPO Financing, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 356)
      - Namibia SWAPO International Relations, 1982-1988 (Box 30, Folder 357)
      - Namibia SWAPO Programs/Assess, 1977-1986 (Box 30, Folder 358)
      - Namibia SWAPO US Registration, 1981-1983 (Box 31, Folder 359)
    - Niger - Somalia
      - Niger, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 360)
      - Nigeria, 1992-1994 (Box 31, Folder 361-366)
      - Rwanda Crisis, 1990-1995 (Box 32, Folder 367-372)
      - Rwanda (Priority Information), 1994 (Box 32, Folder 373)
      - Rwanda (Priority Information), 1994 (Box 75, Folder 794)
      - Rwanda, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 374 -377)
      - Senegal, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 378)
      - Senegal: Violence (Amnesty International), 1995 (Box 76, Folder 809)
      - Sierra Leone, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 379)
      - Somalia, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 380-383)
      - Somalia, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 384-387)
      - Somalia, 1992 (Box 75, Folder 795)
      - Somalia: National Democratic Institute for International Affairs, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 389)
    - South Africa
      - General, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 390)
      - General, 1989-1993 (Box 35, Folder 391-395)
      - General, 1993-1996 (Box 67, Folder 707-713)
      - South Africa ANC, 1990-1993 (Box 35, Folder 396-398)
      - South Africa ANC, 1993-1995 (Box 36, Folder 399-400a)
      - South Africa Culture, 1991-1994 (Box 36, Folder 401-403)
      - South Africa Destabilization, 1984-1988 (Box 36, Folder 404)
      - South Africa: IMF and Recent Economic Development, 1978-1980 (Box 36, Folder 405-7)
      - South Africa Development, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 408-409)
      - South Africa Economy, 1989-1996 (Box 37, Folder 410-415)
      - South Africa Economics, Military, 1970-1980 (Box 37, Folder 416)
      - South Africa Education, 1989-1994 (Box 37, Folder 417-419)
      - South Africa Education, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 568)
      - South Africa Foreign Relations, 1989-1994 (Box 37, Folder 420-424)
      - South Africa Foreign Relations: Botswana, 1970-73 (Box 37, Folder 425)
      - South Africa Foreign Relations: Britain, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 426)
      - South Africa Freedom of Information Act, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 427)
      - South Africa Freedom of Information Act, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 428)
      - South Africa Health, 1990-1994 (Box 38, Folder 429-432)
      - South Africa: Homelands, 1990-1991 (Box 38, Folder 433-434)
      - South Africa Homelands, 1991-1992 (Box 51, Folder 569)
      - South Africa Homelands, 1993-1994 (Box 38, Folder 435-436)
      - South Africa Inkatha Freedom Party (IFP), 1983, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 437-438)
      - South Africa; Release of Nelson Mandela, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 439)
      - South Africa; Nelson Mandela's Visit to the USA, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 440)
      - South Africa A Round Table discussion with Nelson Mandela, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 441)
      - South Africa Media, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 442)
      - South Africa / Nambia Independence, 1980-1989 (Box 39, Folder 443)
      - South Africa Natal / KwaZulu, 1987-1994 (Box 39, Folder 444-446)
      - South Africa: National Peace Accords, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 447)
      - South Africa "Peace Action" Reports, 1991-1994 (Box 39, Folder 448)
      - South Africa Politics, 1989-1992 (Box 39, Folder 449-454)
      - South Africa Politics, 1991-1992 (Box 40, Folder 455-461)
      - South Africa Politics, 1991-1994 (Box 41, Folder 462-468)
      - South Africa Politics, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 469)
      - South Africa Politics, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 470-476)
      - South Africa Politics: Elections, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 477-479)
      - South Africa Politics: Buthelezi/Inkatha, 1978-1982 (Box 43, Folder 480-481)
      - South Africa Politics: Buthelezi, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 482)
      - South Africa Politics: Buthelezi, 1991-1993 (Box 51, Folder 570)
      - South Africa Politics: Inkatha, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 483)
      - South Africa Political Repression, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 484)
      - South Africa Political Repression/Violence, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 485-487)
      - South Africa Political Repression/Violence, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 571-572)
      - South Africa Program, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 488)
      - South Africa Propaganda, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 488A)
      - South Africa Publications and Documents, 1977-1994 (Box 44, Folder 489-491)
      - South Africa Referendum, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 492)
      - South Africa Religion, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 493)
      - South Africa: SADCC and Security, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 494)
      - South Africa: Sanctions Campaign, 1990-1991 (Box 45, Folder 495)
      - South Africa Sports/Culture, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 496)